{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature", "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History", "question": "United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film", "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music", "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers", "question": "The logo for Snapchat is a Bell.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}